NATHAN BRACHOTTE

React Native Developer

PROFILE



24 years old



Looking for a React/React Native Developer position



Berlin, Germany



+49 176 71224417



nathan.brachotte@gmail.com



/nathan-brachotte

ABOUT ME

After a successful experience at Colorfy GmbH and almost 2 years of React Native experience and a Master Degree's in Software Engineering with High Honours, I'm looking for a new challenge in a company where code quality is a priority.

AWARDS

ICT-SHOWROOM 2017 BEST PROJECT AWARD

Creator, App Developer (ionic 2) and Project Manager Turku, Finland

LANGUAGES



Native



CI



A2- Actively learning



В1

INTERESTS



🏅 Played in several sport clubs



ESN Besançon Volunteer



Squash



WORK EXPERIENCE

February 2018 - now

REACT NATIVE DEVELOPER

Colorfy GmbH - Berlin - Full-time - First 6 months as an intern

Development of IOT-related applications for international clients including Henkel & Skyroam Keywords: IoT, React Native, React, Frontend, TypeScript, REST Api, GraphQl

March 2016 - July 2016

WEB DEVELOPER INTERN

IAD Territoire Digital - Besançon, France - 5-month Internship

Development of a CMS-based website: football-observatory.com Keywords: Spip 3, jQuery, JavaScript, HTML, CSS

May 2014 - June 2014

DELPHI DEVELOPER INTERN

Process Electronic France - Besançon, France - 6-week Internship

Development of an FTP client to preview the company's industrial ovens data.

Keywords: Delphi XE7, FTP, Object Oriented



EDUCATION

September 2016 - August 2018

MASTER'S DEGREE IN SOFTWARE AND SYSTEM ENGINEERING

1st year - Åbo Akademi Turku, Finland - Grade: A (15/20) - with High Honours

Keywords: Software Safety, Software Quality, Software Testing, Parallel Programming, Embedded Systems

2nd year - Université de Franche-Comté, Besançon - Grade A (14/20) - with High Honours Keywords: React Native Project, Internship in Germany, Software Engineering, Functional Testing

September 2015 - June 2016

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

Université de Franche-Comté, France - Grade: B+ (13/20) - with Honours Keywords: Object-Oriented Development, Security, Systems and Network, Databases

September 2013 - June 2015

BTS IRIS - 2-YEAR COMPUTER SCIENCE TECHNICAL DEGREE

Lycée Jules Haag, France - Grade: A+ (16/20) - with Highest Honours

Keywords: Computer Science, Industrial Programming, Economy and Management



PERSONAL PROJECTS

BE THE DJ - WEB APP - SERVER - MOBILE APP (COMING SOON)

A Spotify-powered application that allows people to democratically choose music in events Ongoing development

Frontend: React, Styled-Components, Apollo GraphQl, React Native Backend: NodeJS (ExpressJS), GraphQl + Subscriptions, MongoDB, Mongoose



SKILLS

FRONTEND:

Proficient: React Native, React, JavaScript, REST Api

Familiar: Ionic, Apollo, Styled-Components, Spip

BACKEND:

Familiar: Express.js, Node.js, GraphQL

LANGUAGES:

Proficient: JavaScript, TypeScript

Familiar: C++, Java, Delphi